bestoftheweb.com 2019-03-02

# Best of the Web Trust Seals - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

  * We have created this statement to communicate our commitment to privacy and to ensure that you are comfortable with the measures taken to enhance your experience with us. We are dedicated to providing a safe, secure and enjoyable environment for our users. This statement details our current information gathering procedures, which are subject to change without notice. In order to confirm your understanding of our Privacy Policy, it is suggested that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time. This Privacy Policy covers the following practices: 

    * What personally identifiable information Best of the Web (BOTW) collects.
    * How BOTW uses the information.
    * What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
    * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under BOTW control.
  * ### Information Collection and Use

Best of the Web is the sole owner of the information collected on BestoftheWeb.com

#### Collection

During the BOTW Trust Seal service, we require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and business address, phone number) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

#### Use

##### Profile

We store information that we collect through log files, and via the information provided during the BOTW Verified submission process, to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their account. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the user experience. We DO NOT share your profile with other third parties.

##### Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

##### Display

One of the main components of the BOTW Verified service is the verification of contact information. Some of this information is displayed to the general public when a user clicks on an active trust seal placed on your website. This information currently contains: website url, business mailing address, phone number, email address. We may change the information displayed at our sole discretion.

  * ### Communications From Us

#### Special Offers and Updates

Our customers will occasionally receive information on products, services, or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

#### Service Annoucements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications - these communications are not promotional in nature.

#### Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user’s wishes.

  * ### Sharing

#### Legal Disclaimer

During the BOTW Verified service, we require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and business address, phone number) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

#### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information includes: page views, unique visitors, browsers, and additional broad demographical data. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

  * ### When We Share Users' Personal Information:

#### Third Party Intermediaries

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

#### Business Transitions

In the event Best of the Web goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

#### Trust Seal Pop-Up

When a visitor to your site clicks on the Best of the Web Verified trust seal, the embedded script will cause a pop-up to display your verified Information. This information includes: business phone number, email address, website URL, and mailing address. In the future, we may decide to change what type of information we will display in the pop-up.

  * ### Security

We take every precaution to protect users’ information.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our financial department or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are encouraged to use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Our employees are reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage, in a locked facility.

  * ### Notice of Change

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and/or other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we may post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we may also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
